alldubai.ae 2015-10-12

# Privacy Policy - All Dubai - Your Local Dubai Business Directory

All Dubai (AllDubai.ae) is committed to ensuring that your privacy protected. This statement covers the services provided by AllDubai.ae’s website, and is to inform visitors to this website about what information is collected and how this information is used. If we ask you to provide certain information by which you could be identified, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. For the purposes of this policy, the term “visitor” includes visitors to this website as well as our contributors and advertisers.

This Privacy Policy (together with our Terms and Conditions) explains the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information through our websites located at URLs: www.AllDubai.ae. (“our sites”) operated by AllDubai.ae (“we”, “us”). We are registered in Dubai, United Arab Emirates, under company number 6781287, and with registered offices at Dubai, United Arab Emirates.

This Privacy Policy sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.

## Introduction

All Dubai (AllDubai.ae) respects each individual’s right to personal privacy. We will collect and use information through our Web site only in the ways disclosed in this statement. This statement applies solely to information collected at the All Dubai (AllDubai.ae) Web site.

## Part I. Information Collection

All Dubai (AllDubai.ae) collects information through our Web site at several points. We collect the following information about primary visitors: Users Names, e-mail address and other personal information.

We may also collect information which our users divulge about other people. All Dubai (AllDubai.ae) does not actively market to children, and we never knowingly ask a child under 13 to divulge personal information.

We collect this information through emails and contact forms. The information is collected voluntarily.

We may employ cookies. A cookie is a small text file that our Web server places on a user’s computer hard drive to be a unique identifier. Cookies enable All Dubai (AllDubai.ae) to track usage patterns and deliver customized content to users. Our cookies may have an expiration date. Our cookies do not collect personally identifiable information.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Start Local.

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visits to All Dubai (AllDubai.ae) and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

If you wish, you can delete these cookies from your computer between visits to our website by accessing the settings within your web browser. You can manage these small files yourself via your browser settings, and learn more about cookies by visiting [http://www.aboutcookies.org/](http://www.aboutcookies.org/).

## Part II. Information Usage.

The information collected by All Dubai (AllDubai.ae) will be used for providing users with information. Users who provide information may receive list products, services, email announcements or advertisements.

## Third Party Links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party services or products on our website. These third party sites have their own independent provacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content of these sites. Nevertheless, we seek to protect teh integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these third party sites.

We offer links to other Web sites. Please note: When you click on links to other Web sites, we encourage you to read their privacy policies. Their standards may differ from ours.

If our policy on information collection or uses changes, we will update this notice. We have the right to change this notice at any time.

## Part IV. Problem Resolution

If problems arise, users may contact All Dubai (AllDubai.ae) by using the contact form provided. We are committed to resolving disputes in the shortest time possible.

## Part V. Data Storage and Security

All staff of All Dubai (AllDubai.ae) are dedicated to upholding our privcy policy.

## Updating this privacy statement

All Dubai (AllDubai.ae) reserves the right to update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website. You should therefore check this page from time to time to ensure that you are aware of any changes.

Please also view our Terms & Conditions.
